Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Reagan Books, 1968-1988 (Box 1-133)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle XI, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle XI, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle XI, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle XI, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle XI, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-026. RNC: Natl Tracking Survey of Public Atts Eagle Track I - RNC vers, September 18, 1981 - September 28, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-026. RNC: Natl Tracking Survey of Public Atts Eagle Track I - RNC vers, September 18, 1981 - September 28, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-026. RNC: White House Memorandums, September 18, 1981 - September 28, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-027. RNC: White House Memorandums, October 5, 1981 - October 14, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-027. RNC: Natl Tracking Survey of Public Atts: Eagle Track II, October 5, 1981 - October 14, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-028. RNC: Natl Tracking Survey of Public Atts: Eagle Track III, October 17, 1981 - October 26, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-029. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle Track IV, November 9, 1981 - November 18, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-029. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle Track IV, November 9, 1981 - November 18, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-029. RNC: White House Memorandums, November 9, 1981 - November 18, 1981 (Box 49)
  - 699-002-029. RNC: White House Memorandums, November 9, 1981 - November 18, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-029. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle Track IV, November 9, 1981 - November 18, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-030. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle Track V, November 30, 1981 - December 9, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-030. RNC: White House Memorandums, November 30, 1981 - December 9, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-030. RNC: White House Memorandums, November 30, 1981 - December 9, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-030. RNC: White House Memorandums, November 30, 1981 - December 9, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-031. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes 'Eagle' Track VI, December 13, 1981 - December 16, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-032. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes 'Eagle' Track VII, December 18, 1981 - December 22, 1981 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-033. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, January 11, 1982 - January 19, 1982 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-033. RNC: National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, January 11, 1982 - January 19, 1982 (Box 50)
  - 699-002-034. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, January 28, 1982 - January 31, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-035. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, February 13, 1982 - February 14, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-035. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, February 13, 1982 - February 14, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-035. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, February 13, 1982 - February 14, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-036. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, February 25, 1982 - March 6, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-037. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, March 20, 1982 - March 29, 1982 (Box 51)
  - 699-002-037. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, March 20, 1982 - March 29, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-037. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, March 20, 1982 - March 29, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-037. RNC: A National Tracking Survey of Public Attitudes, March 20, 1982 - March 29, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-038. RNC: Natl. Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes Towards the Media, March 24, 1982 - March 27, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-038. RNC: Natl. Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes Towards the Media, March 24, 1982 - March 27, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-039. RNC: A National Bushfire Survey of Votor's Attitudes, April 1, 1982 - April 2, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-039. RNC: A National Bushfire Survey of Votor's Attitudes, April 1, 1982 - April 2, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-040. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, April 12, 1982 - April 18, 1982 (Box 52)
  - 699-002-040. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, April 12, 1982 - April 18, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-040. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, April 12, 1982 - April 18, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany (plus extra scribblings..), April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 53)
  - 699-002-041. RNC: Survey of Public Opinion in the U.K.and Federal Republic of Germany, April 24, 1982 - May 5, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-042. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voters Attitudes, April 30, 1982 - May 3, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-042. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voters Attitudes, April 30, 1982 - May 3, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-043. RNC: National Telephone Survey, April 26, 1982 - May 10, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-043. RNC: National Telephone Survey 'Spring National, April 26, 1982 - May 10, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-044. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 21, 1982 - May 26, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-044. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 21, 1982 - May 26, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-044. RNC: Summary Data from RNC 9 National Brushfire Survey, May 21, 1982 - May 26, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-045. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes, June 16, 1982 - June 22, 1982 (Box 54)
  - 699-002-045. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes, June 16, 1982 - June 22, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-045. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes, June 16, 1982 - June 22, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-046. RNC: Survey of Public Attitudes in the Federal Republic of Germany, June 30, 1982 - July 9, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-047. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes - 'Emergency National, July 19, 1982 - July 20, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-048. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes, July 16, 1982 - July 19, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-048. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, July 16, 1982 - July 19, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-049. RNC: Post-Speech Brushfire, August 17, 1982 - August 17, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-049. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1982 - August 17, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-049. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1982 - August 17, 1982 (Box 55)
  - 699-002-049. Reagan/Bush: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1982 - August 17, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-050. RNC: Weighted: Race and Education, August 25, 2982 - August 29, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-050. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, August 25, 1982 - August 29, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-050. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, August 25, 1982 - August 29, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-050. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, August 25, 1982 - August 29, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-050. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, August 25, 1982 - August 29, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1982 - September 27, 1982 (Box 56)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1982 - September 27, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Voters' Attitudes, July 19, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Voters' Attitudes, July 19, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1982 - September 27, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-051. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1982 - September 27, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-052. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 14, 1982 - October 16, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-052. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 14, 1982 - October 16, 1982 (Box 57)
  - 699-002-052. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 14, 1982 - October 16, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-052. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 14, 1982 - October 16, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-052. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 14, 1982 - October 16, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-053. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 23, 1982 - October 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-053. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 23, 1982 - October 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-053. RNC: A Study of National Attitudes, October 23, 1982 - October 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-053. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, October 23, 1982 - October 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-054. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, November 23, 1982 - November 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-054. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, November 23, 1982 - November 24, 1982 (Box 58)
  - 699-002-054. RNC: National Brushfire Post-Speech, November 23, 1982 - November 24, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-055. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 4, 1982 - November 8, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-055. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 4, 1982 - November 8, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-055. RNC: A National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 4, 1982 - November 8, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: National Merge of Public Attitudes - Regional Breakouts, September 18, 1981 - July 16, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: National Merge of Public Attitudes - in the West, September 18, 1981 - July 16, 1982 (Box 59)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: National Merge of Public Attitudes - In the Northeast, September 18, 1981 - July 16, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: National Merge of Public Attitudes - In the Midwest, September 18, 1981 - July 16, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: National Merge of Public Attitudes - Regional Breakouts, September 18, 1981 - July 16, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Married Men, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Seperated and Divorced Men, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Widowers, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Single Women, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Married Women, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Single Men, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Widows, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Seperated and Divorced Women, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-056. RNC: Zip Cluster Merge: Seperated and Divorced Women, October 1, 1982 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 60)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: Catholic and Non-Catholic Aggregates, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: Special Cross-Tabulations "Gender Variables,", January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-057. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, January 7, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 61)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-058. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, January 27, 1983 - January 29, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 62)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-059. RNC: National Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes, March 17, 1983 - March 21, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: National Benchmark Study, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A Study of National Attitudes: Summary Data, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 63)
  - 699-002-060. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, April 7, 1983 - April 10, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-061. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey Of Public Attitudes, April 27, 1983 - April 28, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-061. RNC: A National Brushfire Survey Of Public Attitudes, April 27, 1983 - April 28, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-061. RNC: Weighted: Education & Ethnicity (Post-Speech Brushfire), April 27, 1983 - April 28, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-062. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 27, 1983 - May 30, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-062. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 27, 1983 - May 30, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-062. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 27, 1983 - May 30, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-062. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 27, 1983 - May 30, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-062. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 27, 1983 - May 30, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-063. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 25, 1983 - June 27, 1983 (Box 64)
  - 699-002-063. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 25, 1983 - June 27, 1983 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-063. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 25, 1983 - June 27, 1983 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-064. RNC: Flash Results, July 6, 1983 - July 18, 1993 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-064. RNC: Flash Results, July 6, 1983 - July 14, 1993 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-064. RNC: National Tracking, July 20, 1983 - July 25, 1993 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-064. RNC: National Benchmark on Mexico, July 20, 1983 - July 25, 1993 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-064. RNC: National Tracking, July 20, 1983 - July 25, 1993 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-065. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, July 30, 1983 - July 31, 1983 (Box 65)
  - 699-002-065. RNC: National Brushfire of Public Attitudes, July 30, 1983 - July 31, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-065. RNC: Flash Results, July 30, 1983 - July 31, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-065. Reagan/Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in South Carolina, June 1, 1984 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: Flash Results, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: Flash Results, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-066. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, August 17, 1983 - August 22, 1983 (Box 66)
  - 699-002-067. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 6, 1983 - September 9, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-067. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 6, 1983 - September 9, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-067. RNC: Flash Results, September 6, 1983 - September 9, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-068. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, September 13, 1983 - September 19, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-068. RNC: National Tracking of Public Attitudes, September 13, 1983 - September 19, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-068. RNC: Flash Results, September 13, 1983 - September 19, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-069. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1983 - September 25, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-069. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, September 23, 1983 - September 25, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-069. RNC: Flash Results, September 23, 1983 - September 25, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes: Summary Data, October 18, 1983 - October 21, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, October 18, 1983 - October 21, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, October 18, 1983 - October 21, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, October 18, 1983 - October 21, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, October 18, 1983 - October 21, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: Flash Results, October 26, 1983 - October 28, 1983 (Box 67)
  - 699-002-070. RNC: Flash Results, October 26, 1983 - October 28, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-072. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 25, 1983 - November 29, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-072. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 25, 1983 - November 29, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-072. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, November 25, 1983 - November 29, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-072. RNC: Flash Results, November 25, 1983 - November 29, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-073. RNC: A Study of National Attitudes Summary Data, December 1, 1983 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-073. Reagan/Bush '84: "Candidate Perceptions": Transcripts of Focus Groups, February 23, 1984 - February 23, 1984 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-074. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, January 18, 1984 - January 21, 1984 (Box 68)
  - 699-002-074. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, January 18, 1984 - January 21, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-074. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, January 18, 1984 - January 21, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-074. RNC: National Brushfire Survey of Public Attitudes, January 18, 1984 - January 21, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-075. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, February 2, 1984 - February 4, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-075. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, February 2, 1984 - February 4, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-076. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, March 7, 1984 - March 11, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-076. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, March 7, 1984 - March 11, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-076. RNC: Flash Results, March 7, 1984 - March 11, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-076. Reagan/Bush '84: Flash Results, March 7, 1984 - March 11, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-077. RNC: Flash Results, April 4, 1984 - April 7, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-077. Reagan/Bush '84: Flash Results, April 4, 1984 - April 7, 1984 (Box 69)
  - 699-002-077. RNC: Michigan National Benchmark, Reagan-Bush, April 1, 1984 - April 1, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-078. RNC: Flash Results, May 5, 1984 - May 8, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-078. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 5, 1984 - May 8, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-078. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, May 5, 1984 - May 8, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-078. RNC: A Survey of Volunteerism, May 5, 1984 - May 8, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-078. RNC: Flash Results, May 5, 1984 - May 8, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-079. Reagan/Bush '83: National Mail-Out Aggregates, May 1, 1984 - May 1, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-079. Reagan/Bush '84: National Mail-Out Aggregates, May 1, 1984 - May 1, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-080. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 2, 1984 - June 5, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-080. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 2, 1984 - June 5, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-080. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, June 2, 1984 - June 5, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-080. RNC: Flash Results, June 2, 1984 - June 5, 1984 (Box 70)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Benchmark Survey, July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Television Spot Study-"Father & Son," "Bury Your Head," "Convention" and "Newspaper,", July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Television Spot Study-"Father & Son," "Bury Your Head," "Convention" and "Newspaper,", July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Television Spot Study-"Father & Son," "Bury Your Head," "Convention" and "Newspaper,", July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Television Spot Study-"Father & Son," "Bury Your Head," "Convention" and "Newspaper,", July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-081. RNC: Television Spot Study-"Father & Son," "Bury Your Head," "Convention" and "Newspaper,", July 1, 1984 - July 1, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-082. Reagan/Bush '84: A Perceptual Analysis of the Presidential Candidates, March 7, 1984 - April 8, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-082. RNC: A Perceptual Analysis of the Presidential Candidates, March 7, 1984 - April 8, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-082. RNC: A Perceptual Analysis of the Presidential Candidates, March 7, 1984 - April 8, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-083. RNC: National Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes, July 5, 1984 - July 8, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-083. RNC: Flash Results, July 5, 1984 - July 8, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-084. RNC: Television Spot Study "Family Misery Index," "Voting Booth Inflation,", August 20, 1984 - August 20, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-084. RNC: Television Spot Study "Family Misery Index," "Voting Booth Inflation,", August 20, 1984 - August 20, 1984 (Box 71)
  - 699-002-087. RNC: Flash Results, September 3, 1984 - September 8, 1984 (Box 71)